bookmarktracker.com 2003-04-01

# BookmarkTracker.com : Our Privacy Policy

Privacy Statement Summary

BookmarkTracker.com strives to protect your privacy. We realize that your bookmark collection could be some of your most private information and will do all we can to protects its privacy.

  * We will never share, rent, loan or give away your personal information or bookmarks to anyone without your consent. 
  * We will not send you any unwanted mail. You have the opportunity of receiving a weekly email newsletter containing your recent account activity and site announcements however it is completely optional. 
  * We wont allow other members to view your personal data or bookmarks without your permission. 

Privacy Statement for BookmarkTracker.com

BookmarkTracker.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site: BookmarkTracker.com. 

Our site (and many other sites) uses cookies to keep track of your session and improve your user experience. These "cookies" are small bits of information stored on your computer, not on our servers. These cookies merely contain a session identifier and will never contain any of your personal information or your password.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (such as name and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about their account activity and site announcements. These announcements may sometimes contain promotional material from our sponsors and partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Our site's registration form also collects optional demographic information such as approximate age, zip code and country. Demographic information can be updated at any time in the user options section of our web site.

We collection information about your interests and hobbies. For example we may determine that, because you have many web sites about golf in your bookmark collection, you are interested in golf. We may use that information to deliver targeted advertising about golfing products to you. This information would never be released to our advertisers. The only information the advertiser would receive is that a certain number or percentage of users are interested in golf.

We collection aggregated information about our users. This information is completely anonymous and cannot be traced back to any particular user. For example, we may provide a list of what web sites are most commonly bookmarked by our users. We may provide this data to our partners or advertisers but they would only know that a certain percentage of users have bookmarked a particular web site. They would never receive any of your personally identifiable information without your approval.

This site contains links to other sites. BookmarkTracker.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Furthermore, when you click on a link to visit another site, we will record that visit in order to provide you with the ability to sort bookmarks by most visited and to help you determine which of your links are more used than others.

We may use this information to suggest other web sites and bookmarks that you may be interested in. For example, if we determined that you were interested in golfing products, we may display a few golfing product bookmarks along with your bookmarks. If you were not interested in a particular item that we suggested to you, you can easily delete it at any time.

BookmarkTracker.com has "Powered by" and co-branded partners that integrate the BookmarkTracker.com application into their own web sites. Because the majority of these co-branded sites maintain their own user database, BookmarkTracker.com has no authority or responsibility over these partners user databases. BookmarkTracker.com will still use the data from these co-branded sites according to this privacy statement, however has no control over how the partner sites use their own data.

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

If asked by law enforcement or other judicial authorities, we must cooperate with their request (just as any other site would) for information.

In the event that our company assets are bought or transferred, customer information, including personally identifiable information will likely be one of the assets transferred. 

Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We employ the use of encryption and other network security hardware. We periodically review our security measures and policy. We also disallow the use of certain highly venerable user passwords. We highly recommend that you never share your password with anyone. If you share a computer with multiple people or use any publicly accessible computer (such as at a library or school computer lab) we recommend you log off before you leave the computer.

BookmarkTracker.com employees will never ask you for your password. If someone asks you for your password, please report the situation to abuse@BookmarkTracker.com as it is likely someone attempting to fraudulently gain access to you account.

Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to webmaster@BookmarkTracker.com
  2. You can visit the following URL: http://www.BookmarkTracker.com/remove.cfm

Should you wish to completely remove your account information from our database, you can cancel your account by sending an email message to cancel@BookmarkTracker.com. In that event, your user information will be completely removed from our database.

Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email webmaster@BookmarkTracker.com
  2. visit http://www.BookmarkTracker.com/options/

Contacting the Web Site

We also encourage you to read our Terms of Service. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
